[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":57381,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":66431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9825,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":76260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5","3"],"rt":32530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":108796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2626,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":111427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":115507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1092,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":116602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3879,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":120483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1158,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":121643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":125420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1325,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":126747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":129883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<su b>6</sub > 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1095,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":130979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":133691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":134677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2533,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":137212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":892,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":138106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your res ult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":140876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":941,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":141819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":144627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":902,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":145531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":147948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":868,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":148819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17123,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":165948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own invers e under  +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":28659,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":194612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":12131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":206747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1212,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":207963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br />< br /> (R emember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":210481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":856,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":211339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 "],"rt":2702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":214043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":215027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":217331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<s ub>6</su b>.","rt":782,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":218115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":221676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10533,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":232212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be  perform ed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":29475,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":261691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2,  but the re is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":60944,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":322638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":327581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7628,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":335212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Re member,  a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2757,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":337972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":10669,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":348643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":29350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":377995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":19686,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":397684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":405628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3365,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":408995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practi ce quest ion with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":18950,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":427947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":431291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":990,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":432283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2678,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":434963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":440075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":445835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":451252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2757,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":454012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":15806,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":469820,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"The answer is 5 because 4 + 1 = 5, which is less than 9.","explanation_history":["4 +","4 ","4 ","4","The answer is 4 ","The answer is 4","The answer is 5 because 5","The answer is 5 because 4+1 =","The answer is 5 because 4+1 ","The answer is 5 because 4+1","The answer is 5 because 4+","The answer is 5 because 4 + 1 = 5, which is less than 9."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":49754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":519579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"The answer is 3, because 8 + 4 = 12, which is greater than 9. By Subtracting  9 from 1 2 we end up with the result of 3.","explanation_history":["The answer is 3 beeca","The answer is 3 beec","The answer is 3 bee","The answer is 3 be","The answer is 3 b","The answer is 3 ","The answer is 3, because 8 + 4 = 12, which is greater than 9. By Subtracting 9 from 12 we end up with the result of 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":47184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":566766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, when subtracting the 9, we end up with a result of 0.","explanation_history":["The identity under +9 ","The identity under +9","The identity under +","The identity under +9 s ","The identity under +9 s","The id entity u nder +9 ","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 +9","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 +","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 ","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, we end up with a result ","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, we","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, w","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, when subtracting the 9 ","The identity under +9 is 0, as anytime we have an equation such as 8 (+9) 1 = 9, or 6 (+9) 3 = 9, when subtracting the 9, we end up with a result of 0."],"response_history":["Then","The","Th","T","0","0"],"rt":157187,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":723967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":13085,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":737068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":3181,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":740251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3196,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":743450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 + 6 = 9. After subtracting 9 from itself, we end up with a result of 0.","explanation_history":["The inverse of 3 under+","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6 ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 6 + 3 = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3+ = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3  = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 + = 9. After subtracting ","The invers e of 3 u nder (+9) is 6, as 3 +  = 9. After subtracting ","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 + 6 = 9. After subtracting 9 from itself, we end up with th","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 + 6 = 9. After subtracting 9 from itself, we end up with t","The inverse of 3 under (+9) is 6, as 3 + 6 = 9. After subtracting 9 from itself, we end up with a result of 0."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":66904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":810356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) can not be used as identifiers.","explanation_history":["2 is nota generator ","2 is not a generator under (+9) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as you ","2 is not a generator under  (+9), as  you","2 is not a generator under (+9), as yo","2 is not a generator under (+9), as y","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (3, 4, 5, 6, 7 ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (23, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2m3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2m 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2m3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (23, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2,3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8)  ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) can ","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) can","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) ca","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8) c","2 is not a generator under (+9), as (2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 , 8) can  not be used as identifiers."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":460155,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1270528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"3 is not a generator under (+9), as (4, 7, 8) can not be used as identifiers.","explanation_history":["3 is not a generator under (+9), as (4, 7, 8) can not be used as identifiers."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":39607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1310152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"5 is no t a gene rator under (+9) as (3, 5, 7, 8) cannot be used as identifiers.","explanation_history":["5 is not a generator under (+9) as (3, 5, 6","5 is not a generator under (+9) as (3, 5, 7, 8) cannot be used as identifiers."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":38045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1348212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"6 is not a generator under (+9) as (3, 6, 7, 8) cannot be used as identifiers.","explanation_history":["6 s ","6 s","6 s","6 is not a generator under (+9) as (3, 6, 7, 8) cannot be used as identifiers."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":59014,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1407233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like  to ask  you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":35709,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1442955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+_8","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["8","+_8"],"rt":24918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1467879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +_n y = 0","explain":true,"explanation":"The formula for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number in the inverse.","explanation_history":["The inverse T","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x + 4_n","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x + 4_","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x + 4","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x + ","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 as ","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 as","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 a","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 ","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, wit","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, wi","The forumla for an inverse of an element x  under +_ n is x +_n y = 0, w","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, wit","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, wi","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, w","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0, ","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0,","The forumla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number in the inverse.","The forula for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number in the inverse.","The forla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number in the inverse.","The formla for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number in the inverse.","The formula for an inverse of an element x under +_n is x +_n y = 0 with y representing the missing number  in the  inverse."],"response_history":["x |","x + ","x +_n y = 0"],"rt":140391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1608285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I cannot think of any patterns which would apply.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["x +)n","x +)","x ++_","x ++","x +_n ","The pattern is x_","The pattern is x","The pattern is ","I cannot think of any patterns which would apply."],"rt":97506,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1705806,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":20336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1726156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":8710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1734868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":9333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1744203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I am honestly just guessing. I don't understand this question at all...","explanation_history":["if x is not a generator under +n, x does not necessarily a","if x is not a generator under +n, x does not necessarily need to be a divis","if x is not a generator under +n, x does no","I am honestly just guessing./","I am honestly just guessing.","I am honestly just guessing. I don't understand this question at all..."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":127558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1871768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":33737,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1905521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"Since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always be a generat or.","explanation_history":["el","e","x is ","since  x is a generator and you are","since  x is a generator and you ar","since  x is a generator and yo","since  x is a generator and y","since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself ","since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always bea ","since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always bea","since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always be a generator. ","since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always be a generator.","ince  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always be a generator.","Since  x is a generator and we are adding it to itself, it must always be a generator."],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":102613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2008148,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n </sub> x  a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":17770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2025933,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2627,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2028564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"33","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["33"],"rt":3229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2031795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Wha t is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2034580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Algebra"],"rt":13900,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2048483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2054034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2057530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":6294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2063827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4118,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2067947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3373,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2071322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2670,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2073994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free ","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":5398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2079394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No.","No"],"rt":7383,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2086778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":[],"rt":2806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2089586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]